Guide to the J. Arthur (Jesse Arthur) Younger Papers, 1951-1968
Department of Special Collections
- Russia Uses Fishing Boats in Exporting Revolution From Cuba Robert S. Allen and Paul Scott, May 23, 1963 (Page Page A 3263)
- Art Hoppe's Columns, May 27, 1963 (Page Page A 3356)
- The Simplified Test Ban Treaty Hosmer's Test Ban Treaty, May 27, 1963 (Page Page A 3347)
- American Checks and Balances Charles Bruce Gilley, May 28, 1963 (Page Page A 3401)
- The So-Called Bundy-Rostow Agreement Robert S.Allen and Paul Scott, May 28, 1963 (Page Page A 3392)
- Agricultural Chemicals Dr. Daniel G. Aldrich, Jr. Dean of Agriculture at the University of California, May 29, 1963 (Page Page A 3444)
- An American Looks at the Nation Charles Edison, June 3, 1963 (Page Page A 3535)
- Results of the Opinion Poll, June 3, 1963 (Page Page A 3527)
- Drug Safety and Drug Control Dr. L. T. Coggeshall, June 4, 1963 (Page Page A 3568)
- Oil Depletion, June 10, 1963 (Page Page A 3695)
- The President Should Stay Home Eldon Griffiths and John M. Hightower, June 10, 1963 (Page Page 9937)
- Television and Children Robert W. Sarnoff, June 10, 1963 (Page Page A 3707)
- Socialistic Conservation Jack Pickett, June 11, 1963 (Page Page A 3746)
- Who Are the Real Fright Peddlers James B. Utt, M. C., June 13, 1963 (Page Page A 3823-26)
- Report on Telstar American Telephone and Telegraph Company, June 18, 1963 (Page Page A 3867)
- Town Meeting of the World Using Telstar Mr. Frank Stanton, President, C. B. S., June 19, 1963 (Page Page A 3893)
- Arthur Hoppe's Columns, June 19, 1963 (Page Page A 3907)
- The Trigger Is Pulled on the Cocked Pistol Jack Pickett in The California Farmer, June 24, 1963 (Page Page A 4001)
- Shortcomings in Public Affairs of the Government Terrence O'Flaherty and Geo. Dixon, July 8, 1963 (Page Page A 4219)
- Art Hoppe, July 8, 1963 (Page Page A 4213)
- Religious Freedom in America and the Supreme Court Decision Mrs. L. Hosmer, July 10, 1963 (Page Page A 4290)
- Bracero Loss Means a Crop Loss in San Mateo Article from the San Mateo Times., July 11, 1963 (Page Page A 4336)
- Report on Proposed Federal Legislation To Suspend Equal Broadcasting Time Requirements For the 1964 Presidential Campaign. Report made by the Committee on the Federal Legis. of the Assoc. of the Bar of the City of New York., July 15, 1963 (Page Page A 4406-7)
- There Goes Free Enterprise Mr. Donald Rogers, Business and Financial editor of the New York Herald Tribune, July 16, 1963 (Page Page A 4464)
- Kennedy's Popularity Wm. F. Buckley in the S. F Examiner., July 17, 1963 (Page Page A 4492)
- Town Meeting of the World C.B.S. T. V. broadcast via Telstar., July 18, 1963 (Page Page A 4560)
- Art Hoppe, July 23, 1963 (Page Page A 4628)
- A Purported Conversation Between Khruschev and the Chinese Delegation Weekly Review of London., July 23, 1963 (Page Page A 4604)
- Russian Pledges Letter to President Roosevelt From Maxim Litvinoff, U.S.S.R., July 25, 1963 (Page Page A 4717)
- The Common Denominator Robert C. Tyson, U.S.S., July 29, 1963 (Page Page A 4776)
- J.A.Y.'s comments on Cuba and the Cold War, July 29, 1963 (Page [UNK])
- Trial in the Rose Garden Geo. Dixon, D. C. Post, August 5, 1963 (Page Page A 4969)
- Bootleg Truckers Flourish, August 5, 1963 (Page Page A 4964)
- Communists, Following Mao's Rules, Soft Pedal Marxism in Early Stages of Guerilla Revolt by [UNK], August 6, 1963 (Page Page A 5072)
- The Approach To Russ Weak Point Dr. Stefan Possony University of Stanford, August 14, 1963 (Page Page A 5182)
- Bobby Kennedy's Totalitarian Press Lucius Beebe, San Francisco Chronicle, August 14, 1963 (Page Page A 5173)
- Arthur Hoppe's Columns, August 27, 1963 (Page Page A 5507)
- A Miss in Panama Rowland Evans and Robt. Novak of the POST writing on Ambassador Farland of Panama., August 27, 1963 (Page Page A 5489)
- Unbalanced Government Dr. Harley L. Lutz of Princeton University., August 28, 1963 (Page Page A 5519)
- Gary Boldwater, Boy American Art Hoppe, September 5, 1963 (Page Page A 5621)
- A tough Policy To Swallow Art Hoppe, September 5, 1963 (Page Page A 5615)
- NATO and the Test Ban Trety Constantine Brown, writer for the Star, September 9, 1963 (Page Page A 5647)
- Arthur Hoppe's Columns, September 9, 1963 (Page Page A 5658)
- Q.E.D. Dr. Paul Ludwig, Chevy Chase Presbyterian Church, Washington, D. C., September 9, 1963 (Page Page A 5662)
- Why the Far East Is Vitally Important, Mr. Robt. R. Gros, Vice President, P. G. E., S. F., September 10, 1963 (Page Page A 5688)
- J. A. Y.'s Comments on Mental Health, September 10, 1963 (Page Page 15792)
- Art Hoppe's Columns, September 16, 1963 (Page Page A 5802)
- Values in a Vacum Dean Erwin N. Griswold, Harvard Law School in a talk at the Univ. of Utah, September 16, 1963 (Page Page A 5810)
- Beware the Test Ban Craig Hosmer, September 23, 1963 (Page Page A 5582)
- [UNK], September 25, 1963 (Page Page A 6040)
- Who's fighting whom? - editorial in the Evening Star, Sept. 25, 1963 (Page Page A 6048)
- A Question of Who Geo. Dixon in the Star, September 30, 1963 (Page Page A 6121)
- Just Plain Jack Is Back Art Hoppe, September 30, 1963 (Page Page A 6119)
- British See Taint on White House by Rene MacColl, September 30, 1963 (Page Page A 6113)
- Vietnam Trip Linked to Politics Joseph Kraft from the Star, September 30, 1963 (Page Page A 6109)
- Unifying the Common Carrier Industry W. G. White, Pres. of Consolidated Freightways., October 2, 1963 (Page Page A 6177)
- The Landis case, JAY's comments, October 1, 1963 (Page Page 17457)
- OK. Who took our foreign aid? Art Hoppe, October 3, 1963 (Page Page A 6222)
- Radio and T.V. audience ratings Chas. P. Howe, Jr., October 7, 1963 (Page Page A 6243)
- Bad news - Post editorial, October 8, 1963 (Page Page A 6294)
- Pay raise for Congress, October 14, 1963 (Page Page 18442)
- [UNK] Right gts U.S. Subsidy
- Russia, Tito, and China- Intelligence Digest of North Cerney House, Cirencester, Gloucestershire, England., October 15, 1963 (Page Page A 6445)
- Art Hoppe's Columns, October 17, 1963 (Page Page A 6512)
- Art Hoppe's Coulmns, October 24, 1963 (Page Page A 6643)
- U.S. Press Network-editorial from the San Diego Union., October 28, 1963 (Page Page A 6666)
- Business Citenship in Perspective-Dr. Shane MacCarthy., October 28, 1963 (Page Page A 6665)
- Art Hoppe's Columns, October 30, 1963 (Page Page A 6756)
- The Prince-JAY's Comments on Machiavelli's book as a parallel to our sail of Wheat to Russia., November 6, 1963 (Page Page 20100)
- Art Hoppe in England, November 7, 1963 (Page Page A 6944)
- Boxing Commissioner Kenneth C. Kennedy article by George Clifford in the Washington Daily News., November 13, 1963 (Page Page A 7037)
- Kermit Roosevelt's Questions on Foreign Policy Mr. Roosevelt's address to the Commonwealth Club, November 13, 1963 (Page Page A 7040)
- The Point of It All, Dr. Paul Ludwig, Pastor of the Chevy Chase Presbyterian Church., November 18, 1963 (Page Page A7107)
- Situation Report Mr. Martin Agronsky, November 19, 1963 (Page Page A7144)
- Johnsons Liberals Mr. Evans and Novak in the Washington Post., December 3, 1963 (Page Page A 7375)
- JAY's Comments on JFK., December 5, 1963 (Page Page 22315)
- JANUARY 1964:
  - When and How to Cut Federal Taxes Article by Roswell Magill., Jan. 8th (Box Box 8-10, Page Page A 31)
  - The Present Situation in the Executive Dept. by A. Hoppe, Jan. 8th (Page Page A 39)
  - The Evolution of an Instant Statesman by Lucius Beebe, Jan. 8th (Page Page A 46)
  - JAY's Comments on Proposed Legislation to Correct Inequities in Our Monetary and Fiscal Policies., Jan. 13 (Page Page 276)
  - Art Hoppe's Columns, Jan. 13 (Page Page A 110)
  - The Resurgence of the Railroads and Their Importance To Economic Growth by Stuart Saunders, Chr. of the Board, Penn. Railroad., Jan. 13 (Page Page A 114)
  - JAY's Comments on Amendments to Federal Airport Act, Jan. 14 (Page Page 385)
  - JAY's Eulogy to Cong. Baker, Jan. 16 (Page Page 556)
  - After $3 Billion U.S. Aid, Tito Closer to USSR, Than Any Time Since Stalin's Death. Address by Milord Drachkovitch, Senior Member of the Hoover Institution., Jan. 22 (Page Page A 253)
  - Faith, Hope and Charity Editorial from the Star, Jan 23 (Page Page A 271)
  - JAY's Comments on Beef Imports, Jan. 23 (Page Page 956)
  - JAY's Comments on the Bobby Baker Invertigation, Jan. 28 (Page Page 1116)
  - Suspension of Equal Time Provision of the Communications Act From the Washington Post by Julius Duscha., Feb. 3 (Page Page 1641)
  - The Baker Affair, A Midge to LBJ. From the Post by Mr. Childs., Feb. 4 (Page Page A 503)
  - The T. V. Debate Ban Would Be Unfair, Feb. 5 (Page Page A 532)
  - The So-Called Tax Reduction Bill Remarks on the Floor by JAY., Feb. 7 (Page Page 2446)
  - state Local Finances: Recurring Crisis or Gradual Evolution by C. Lowell Harriss, Prof. of Economics-Columbia., Feb. 10 (Page Page A 641)
  - Where There Is No Vision, The People Perish by L. Hosmer., Feb. 10 (Page Page A 637)
  - Banking Profits and Economic Growth, Feb. 10 (Page Page A 685)
  - What Really Happened, Feb. 24 (Page Page A 863)
  - Length or Frequency of Broadcast Commercials JAY's Remarks., Feb. 27 (Page Page A body, Page Page 3741)
  - Tax Cut Hopes Editorial from the Evening Star, March 2 (Page Page A 1007)
  - Does Government Spending Help Economic Growth by Ira Ellis, Economist for E.I. du Pont Nemours & Co., March 2 (Page Page A 1001)
  - Economy and the Electricity Bill-Ol'Elbie saves $4.32 on Lights but Owes $67, 000 for Telephone by Art Hoppe, March 2 (Page Page A 998)
  - Spend or Save David Lawrence from the U. S. News & World Report, March 3 (Page Page A 1053)
  - Untold Story of Wheat Crisis Mr. Victor Riesel, New York Journal-American, March 3 (Page Page A 1047)
  - Cut Revenues To Reduce Spending by Gould Lincoln, Washington Star, March 4 (Page Page A 1106)
  - The People's Choice, Mr. Whatshisname Art Hoppe, March 4 (Page Page A 1237)
  - JAY's Remarks on the Federal Pay Raise, March 12 (Page Page 4938)
- MARCH:
  - Japan Will Take No Precipitate Action on Red China-Assurance by Ambassador Takeuchi, address to the Commonwealth Club by the Ambassador., 3-16-64 (Page Page A 1352)
  - Choosing a Vice President, Chas. Bartlett, Wash.Star, 3-16-64 (Page Page A 1349)
  - Whitewash, editorial in Wash. Star., 3-16-64 (Page Page A 1340)
  - The Dangerous Game of `Let's Pretend, Readers Digest, Allen Drury., 3-18-64 (Page Page A 1414)
  - Is America Heading for Total War, Jenken L. Jones, Redwood City Tribune., 3-18-64 (Page Page A 1405)
  - Controversy in Capitol: Cultural Center Arousing Rancor Before It's Begun, Patricia W. Reisinger, 3-23-64 (Page Page A 1502)
  - How To Begin Smoking, Art Hoppe., 3-23-64 (Page Page A 1483)
  - Still Unanswered in the Baker Case, U.S. News & World Report., 3-25-64 (Page Page A 1515)
- APRIL:
  - It's Time for United Statesmanship, Leo Burnett, Chicago., 4-9-64 (Page Page A 1769)
  - Cost of Operations of House on Thursday Last., 4-15-64 (Page Page 7748-49)
  - Regulatory Plight of Natural Gas Producers., 4-15-64 (Page Page 7755)
  - ART HOPPE'S: The White House Isn't Brilliant; Now Is the Time For All Good Caterers; The Gayest Tribe in Washington; Motherhood Gets You in Trouble., 4-20-64 (Page Page A 1947)
  - ART HOPPE'S: Mr. Salinger's Secret Weapon; Elbie Jay Puts His Foot Down., 4-22-64 (Page Page A 2014)
  - The War on Poverty & The Executive Branch, American Taxpayers Association, Inc., 4-22-64 (Page Page A 2024)
  - Trade With Soviet Russia, R.G. Follis, Standard Oil Co. of Calif., 4-29-64 (Page Page A 2143)
  - General De Gaulle's Addrsss, over radio & TV., 4-30-64 (Page Page A 2196)
- MAY:
  - The Baker Noninvestigation, Roscoe Drummond, Washington Post., 5-4-64 (Page Page A 2239)
  - President's Speech on Economy, David Lawrency, Evening Star., 5-4-64 (Page Page A 2227)
  - ART HOPPE'S: Will The Dogs Go To Elbie Jay?; Nobody is the People's Choice; Three Cheers for Nobody; Nobody Turns Fat Cats Away., 5-5-64 (Page Page A 2258-60)
  - Liberals Distrust Johnson, Richard Wilson., 5-5-64 (Page Page A 2264)
  - Forcasting Purchasing and Business Trends, Dr. John H. Hoagland., 5-5-64 (Page Page A 2267-68)
  - Against Poverty Since 1776, Charles B. Shuman., 5-5-64 (Page Page A 2274)
  - He Takes the Rap, editorial from Sunday Star., 5-11-64 (Page Page A 2387)
  - Is This the Way to Fight the War Against Poverty? Charles Stevenson, May issue, Readers Digest., 5-13-64 (Page Page A 2465-67)
  - Pay Your Debts - A Sermon, Captain James E. Reaves., 5-18-64 (Page Page A 2556)
  - Gold Medal for Henry J. Kaiser., 5-18-64 (Page Page 10764)
  - International Reciprocity for Amateur Radio Operators., 5-18-64 (Page Page 10777)
  - ART HOPPE'S: Let's Hear It From LBJ - Yelp! Yelp! Yelp!; Somber Pierre of Happy Al?; Any News is Good News-Elbie Jay., 5-19-64 (Page Page A 2621)
  - Hospital and Medical Facilities Amendments of 1964., 5-25-64 (Page Page 11408-9)
  - Correction of Rollcall., 5-26-64 (Page Page 11562)
  - Increase in Federal Deposit and Savings Insurance., 5-27-64 (Page Page 11655 & 11664)
- JUNE:
  - Can a Company Afford To Fight an Antitrust Suit? Daniel Peterkin, Jr., Pres. of Morton Salt., 6-2-64 (Page Page A 2940-41)
  - A Memorial Day Letter by Senator Norris Cotton., 6-2-64 (Page Page A 2942-43)
  - Morning Report, Mr. Abe Millinkoff, SF Chronicle., 6-4-64 (Page Page A 3001-2)
  - The Case of Otto F. Otepka, Cecil Holland, Wash. Star., 6-8-64 (Page Page A 3041-43)
  - ART HOPPE'S: Be Popular, Be President; Poverty is Always With Us; Pay Tribute to LBJ; On E-Z Terms and The: Latest Trend in Political Machines., 6-8-64 (Page Page A 3052-53)
  - Modernization of Federal Salary Systems., 6-11-64 (Page Page 13072)
  - Failure of Rules Committee to Report H. R. 9903, Transportation Act of 1958, Mr. Morris Forgash., 6-15-64 (Page Page 13280-84)
  - Domocratic Gloom is Puzzling, David Lawrence., 6-15-64 (Page Page A 3206-07)
  - House Resolution 746, Making in Order Consideration of H. R. 11376, Excise and Tax Rate Extension Act of 1964., 6-17-64 (Page Page 13558)
  - ART HOPPE'S: Barry Would Rather Be Right., 6-17-64 (Page Page A 3287-88)
  - The Reapportionment Decision, David Lawrence and William S. White, Washington Star., 6-18-64 (Page Page A 3340-41)
  - Europeans Believe That U.S. Hac Decided to Back Down in Southeast Asia, Frank J. Johnson, Washington Report of the American Security Council., 6-23-64 (Page Page A 3424-25)
  - By the End of the 20th Century, David Sarnoff, Fortune Magazine., 6-25-64 (Page Page A 3491-92)
  - Creation of a Committee of Inquiry., 6-29-64 (Page Page 14753)
  - Public Rules & Resolutions - H. Res. 794., 6-29-64 (Page Page 14788)
  - The Game of Symbols, Abe Millinkoff, SF Chronicle., 6-29-64 (Page Page A 3529)
  - School Prayer, Rev. Lowell I. Torgerson, Ascension Lutheran Church of SF., 6-29-64 (Page Page A 3532-33)
  - Polls as Political Weapon, William S. White, Washington Star., 6-30-64 (Page Page A 3583-84)
- JULY:
  - Special Committee to Investigate Campaign Expenditures., 7-2-64 (Page Page 15368-69)
  - Public Rules & Resolutions - H. R. 11877., 7-1-64 (Page Page 15131)
  - An Attempt to Stifle Criticism of the Administration, Mr. Luther W. Martin, Radio Station KTTR, ROlla, Mo., 7-20-64 (Page Page A 3743)
  - Equal Time? Clarence Jones, Radio Station WQIZ, St. George, S.C., 7-20-64 (Page Page A 3749)
  - A Cold Day for Power of the Press, Lucius Beebe, SF Chronicle., 7-20-64 (Page Page A 3753)
  - Senator Goldwater, Intelligence Digest, Gloucestershire, England., 7-21-64 (Page Page A 3778)
  - Right to be Lonley in a Crowd, Richard Wilson, Washington Star., 7-21-64 (Page Page A 3786)
  - Treasury & Post Office Departments, the Executive Office of the President, & Certain Independent Agencies, 7-28-64 (Page Page 16632)
  - The Impact of U.S. Foreign Economic Policy on the War on Poverty, Trade Relations Council of the US, Inc., 7-28-64 (Page Page A 3954-56)
  - The Nib Does It, article in Newsweek, Aug., 7-31-64; 3 issue. (Page Page A 4017)
- AUGUST:
  - A Treacherous Truth, Dr. Frederick Brown Harris, Chaplain, U.S. Senate, Washington Star., 8-3-64 (Page Page A 4061)
  - U.S. Inflation Since 1933, Lawrence Sullivan, Christian Economic., 8-4-64 (Page Page A 4099-4100)
  - Let's Face Up to the Truth, Charles L. Could, at SF Rotary Club., 8-5-64 (Page Page 17653-56)
  - The Mounting Scandal of Urban Renewal, John Dowdy, U.S. Rep., Texas., 8-11-64 (Page Page A 4239-40)
  - The Golden Years - Retired, His Wife Quizzes Company, Thomas Collins., 8-11-64 (Page Page A 4243)
  - Marking of Steel Containers., 8-12-64 (Page Page 18607)
  - Authorizing Free Transportation of Guides or Dogs Guides Accompaning Blind Persons Aboard Aircraft., 8-12-64 (Page Page 18612)
  - Time to Restrain the Courts, William S. White, Washington Evening Star., 8-14-64 (Page Page A 4317)
  - Elbie Jay Has a Party, Art Hoppe, SF Chronicle; This Wild West - Happy Underdog in a Tub of Water, Lucius Beebe In Tints of Rose, George N. Crocker, SF Examiner., 8-31-64 (Page Page A 4513)
- SEPTEMBER:
  - Talk of Frederick R. Kappel at Annual Meeting of American Bar Association in New York., 9-2-64 *9-3-64 (Page Page 20806)
  - Convention Arrangements Inefficient `Nightmare', Betty Beale, Washington Star., 9-8-64 (Page Page A 4632)
  - Sine Die Adjournment of the Congress., 9-10-64 (Page Page 21216)
  - The 150th Anniversary of the `Star Spangled Banner.', 9-16-64 (Page Page 21527)
  - Art Hoppe's Columns., 9-16-64 (Page Page A 4722)
  - Encourage Physicians to Practice in Certain Areas., *9-3-64 (Page Page 20952)
  - Supplemental Appropriation Bill, 1965., 9-22-64 (Page Page 21725)
  - `Some Aspects of American Foreign Policy' - By the Honorable Robert D. Murphy., 9-22-64 (Page Page 21743-47)
  - Loans to Students of Optometry., 9-30-64 (Page Page 22449)
- CONGRESSIONAL RECORD - clippings 196589th Congress
  - JANUARY: (Box Box 8-11, 8-12)
    - Uruguay: A Wel-Fairy Tale, Time, Nove. 27, 1964., 1-5 (Page Page A 16)
    - When Ends Justify Means, by Dean Acheson in Wall Street Journal, Dec. 11, 1964., 1-5 (Page A 19)
    - Television Programing, Herald Tribune, NY City., 1-11-65 (Page A 94)
    - Our Transportation System, by Morris Forgash., 1-12-65 (Page 609-14)
    - The Transportation Picture, Washington Star January 17, 1965., 1-19-65 (Page A 221)
    - Panal Discussion on the International Situation in the Far East, Commonwealth Club of California., 1-25-65 (Page 1096-97)
    - Federal Domination a Way of Life, Redwood City Tribune,;-19-65., 1-26-65 (Page A 283-84)
  - FEBRUARY
    - Many Versions of the Great Society, James S. Kemper, Jr., 2-1-65 (Page 1600-01)
    - Churchill Funeral Raises Question, David Lawrence., 2-3-65 (Page A 443-44)
    - The Greatest Growth Center, Wall Street Journal 1 Feb. 1., 2-4-65 (Page A 464-65)
    - Oh, We'd Die for Whatshisname, Art Hoppe., 2-4-65 (Page A 462)
    - No Pity for the Provident, Wall Street Journal 2-3., 2-8-65 (Page A 483)
    - Home Rule? Washington Sunday Star, Feb. 7., 2-8-65 (Page A 486)
    - What is Being Done in the Name of the Great Society, Washington Post, Joseph Alsop & George Dixon., 2-17-65 (Page 2851-52)
    - The Farm Labor Situation in Florida, JAY'S REMARKS., 2-18-65 (Page 2908-9)
    - Inter-American Development Bank, 2-22-65 (Page 3217-18)
    - Review & Outlook, Wall Street Journal, Feb. 18, 2-23-65 (Page A 768)
    - Thinking Things Over Vermont Royster, Wall Street Journal, Feb. 18., 2-23-65 (Page A 772)
  - MARCH
    - Reapportionment, 3-1-65 (Page 3795)
    - Realism of Communism, Mr. Robert Stanton., 3-1-65 (Page 3796)
    - The Gold Reserve, 3-1-65 (Page A 863)
    - British Doctor: Why I Refused, 3-1-65 (Page A 865)
    - A Plug From the White House, George Dixon, 3-1-65 (Page A 867)
    - Jay's remarks - Appalachian Regional Development Act of 1965., 3-2-65 (Page Pg.3842)
    - Mystery in Drive For School Aid, David Lawrence, 3-3-65 (Page A 938)
    - The Incredible Parallel, Louise Hosmer., 3-3-65 (Page 3952-54)
    - Communist Activities in Latin America, Jeremiah O'Leary, Washington Star., 3-8-65 (Page 4267-68)
    - Drug Abuse Control Amendments of 1965 JAY'S remarks., 3-9-65 (Page 4300-02)
    - Drug Abuse Control Amendments of 1965 JAY'S remarks., 3-10-65 (Page 4575)
    - Capitol Punishment: President Goldwater, Art Buchwald - Washington Post., 3-10-65 (Page A 1081)
    - New Castro Fortifications Ring U.S. Naval Base at Guantanamo, James D. Hittle, Sunday Star., 3-15-65 (Page A1148)
    - Mr. Joad Reports from the Front, Art Hoppe, 3-15-65 (Page A1150)
    - Why Let Every Dick, Tom, and Harry in our Country, Jenkin L. Jones, RC Tribune, 3-24-64 (Page A1385-86)
    - JAY'S REMARKS - Providing for Consideration of H.R. 2362, Elementary and Secondary Education Act of 1965., 3-26-65 (Page 5919-5929)
  - APRIL
    - Voting Discrimination and Grant & Lee at Appomattox-100 Years Ago, editorials in Sunday Star., 4-5-65 (Page 6651)
    - South Africa: A Bright Spot on a Dark Continent, H.L.T. Taswell., 4-5-65 (Page A1650-51)
    - A Bombshell in Rio, Rowland Evans & Robert Novak., 4-12-65 (Page A1768)
    - House Committee on Un-American Activities to Investigate the Ku Klux Klan., 4-8-65 (Page 7188-89)
    - Uncreative Federalism, Wall Street Journal., 4-21-65 (Page A 1903)
    - Vietnam Crisis, Richard Nixon., 4-21-65 (Page A 1912-14)
    - United States to Hold Rein on Projects, Richard Wilson, 4-23-65 (Page A 1925)
    - The New Medicare Tax, Richard L. Lyons, Wash. Post., 4-26-65 (Page 8096)
    - In Perpetual Childhood, Wall StreetJournal., 4-26-65 (Page A 1944)
    - President Johnson's Position on Poll Tax., 4-28-65 (Page 8441)
  - MAY:
    - Resignation of Herbert W. Klotz, Louis M. Kohlmeier., 5-3-65 (Page Pg. 8862-63)
    - Why Crime Marches Onl Washington Star., 5-3-65 (Page A2087)
    - False Guide for Deficit Spending, Lawrence Fertig., 5-3-65 (Page A2107)
    - The Choice You Make, Captain James E. Reaves., 5-6-65 (Page 9360-61)
    - Hoppe's Columns - Mr. Joad Goes to Wash. and Let's Not Forget the Forgotten, Art Hoppe, SF Chronicle., 5-11-65 (Page A2297)
    - Shasta Daisy as the National Flower, Mrs. Esther B. McDonald., 5-17-65 (Page 10263)
    - The Conditions For Economic Growth and Development: Their Relative Importance and Timing, Karl Brandt., 5-17-65 (Page 10275-79)
    - Telegram sent to the Presidentby Members of the Stanford University Faculity., 5-19-65 (Page A2489)
    - If Vietcong Keeps Sanctuary in North Viet Nam It Can Call the Tune, E.G. Wheeler., 5-19-65 (Page A2493)
    - JAY's REMARKS - Authorizing Appropriations for the AEC 1966., 5-20-65 (Page 10762)
    - Elbie Jay Battles the Munsters, Art Hoppe, 5-20-65 (Page A2514)
    - Protesting Too Little, Wall Street Journal., 5-24-65 (Page A2569)
    - Repairs to Avoid Repairs, Wall Street Journal., 5-24-65 (Page A2570)
    - University of California Listed as First Test of Red Plan to Embarrass Nation's Univeristies and Colleges, Dr. Roswell G. Ham, 5-26-65 (Page A2673)
  - JUNE:
    - Can Government Guarantee Prosperity? Robert C. Tyson, Realities May End US Optimism, Constantine Brown., 6-1-65 (Page A2784)
    - Free Interprise Has to be Fought For in This Country Dispite its Success, Henry R. Luce., 6-2-65 (Page 11914)
    - Appointment of Administrator of the Federal Aviation Agency, JAY'S REMARKS, 6-3-65 (Page 11951-60)
    - Spouses' Annuities Under Railroad Retirement Act of 1937 JAY'S REMARKS, 6-7-65 (Page 12176-78)
    - Use of Additives in Confectionery, JAY'S REMARKS, 6-7-65 (Page 12179 & 81)
    - Implementing the Convention for the Safety of Life At Sea, JAY'S REMARKS, 6-7-65 (Page 12183)
    - Morning Report, Abe Mellinkoff., 6-7-65 (Page A2906)
    - Arthur Hoppe's Columns, 6-7-65 (Page A2909)
    - Washington's Winning the War, Arthur Hoppe., 6-8-65 (Page A2949)
    - Establishing a Department of Housing and Urban Development, and for Other Purposes. JAY'S REMARKS, 6-15-65 (Page 13217+18)